<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ownershipDocument>

    <schemaVersion>X0306</schemaVersion>

    <documentType>4</documentType>

    <periodOfReport>2019-01-22</periodOfReport>

    <notSubjectToSection16>0</notSubjectToSection16>

    <issuer>
        <issuerCik>0001084577</issuerCik>
        <issuerName>CYREN Ltd.</issuerName>
        <issuerTradingSymbol>CYRN</issuerTradingSymbol>
    </issuer>

    <reportingOwner>
        <reportingOwnerId>
            <rptOwnerCik>0001763709</rptOwnerCik>
            <rptOwnerName>Kushwaha Rajveer</rptOwnerName>
        </reportingOwnerId>
        <reportingOwnerAddress>
            <rptOwnerStreet1>C/O CYREN INC.,</rptOwnerStreet1>
            <rptOwnerStreet2>1430 SPRING HILL ROAD, SUITE 330</rptOwnerStreet2>
            <rptOwnerCity>MCLEAN</rptOwnerCity>
            <rptOwnerState>VA</rptOwnerState>
            <rptOwnerZipCode>22102</rptOwnerZipCode>
            <rptOwnerStateDescription></rptOwnerStateDescription>
        </reportingOwnerAddress>
        <reportingOwnerRelationship>
            <isDirector>1</isDirector>
            <isOfficer>0</isOfficer>
            <isTenPercentOwner>0</isTenPercentOwner>
            <isOther>0</isOther>
            <officerTitle></officerTitle>
            <otherText></otherText>
        </reportingOwnerRelationship>
    </reportingOwner>

    <nonDerivativeTable>
        <nonDerivativeTransaction>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Ordinary Shares</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <transactionDate>
                <value>2019-01-22</value>
            </transactionDate>
            <deemedExecutionDate></deemedExecutionDate>
            <transactionCoding>
                <transactionFormType>4</transactionFormType>
                <transactionCode>A</transactionCode>
                <equitySwapInvolved>0</equitySwapInvolved>
            </transactionCoding>
            <transactionTimeliness></transactionTimeliness>
            <transactionAmounts>
                <transactionShares>
                    <value>10000</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F1"/>
                </transactionShares>
                <transactionPricePerShare>
                    <value>0</value>
                </transactionPricePerShare>
                <transactionAcquiredDisposedCode>
                    <value>A</value>
                </transactionAcquiredDisposedCode>
            </transactionAmounts>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>10000</value>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>D</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeTransaction>
        <nonDerivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Ordinary Shares</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>27586733</value>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>See Footnotes</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F2"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F3"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F4"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F5"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F6"/>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeHolding>
    </nonDerivativeTable>

    <footnotes>
        <footnote id="F1">These shares were issued as a restricted stock unit grant to the Reporting Person by the issuer under the issuer's 2016 Non-Employee Director Equity Incentive Plan. The restricted stock units vest in four equal annual installments beginning on January 22, 2020.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F2">The Reporting Person is an indirect beneficial owner of Warburg Pincus (Bermuda) Private Equity GP Ltd., a Bermuda exempted company (&quot;WP Bermuda GP&quot;), and a Member and Managing Director of Warburg Pincus LLC, a New York limited liability company (&quot;WP LLC&quot;). The Warburg Pincus Entities (as defined below) collectively own 27,586,733 ordinary shares, as of the date hereof.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F3">All ordinary shares indicated as indirectly owned by the Reporting Person are included because of his affiliation with the Warburg Pincus Entities, due to which Mr. Kushwaha may be deemed to have an indirect pecuniary interest (within the meaning of Rule 16a-1 under the Securities and Exchange Act of 1934, as amended) in an indeterminate portion of the ordinary shares owned by the Warburg Pincus Entities. Mr. Kushwaha disclaims beneficial ownership of all ordinary shares attributable to the Warburg Pincus Entities except to the extent of his direct pecuniary interest therein.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F4">The &quot;Warburg Pincus Funds&quot; are Warburg Pincus (Callisto) Private Equity XII (Cayman), L.P., Warburg Pincus (Europa) Private Equity XII (Cayman), L.P., Warburg Pincus (Ganymede) Private Equity XII (Cayman), L.P., Warburg Pincus Private Equity XII-B (Cayman), L.P., Warburg Pincus Private Equity XII-D (Cayman), L.P., Warburg Pincus Private Equity XII-E (Cayman), L.P., Warburg Pincus XII Partners (Cayman), L.P., and WP XII Partners (Cayman), L.P. The Warburg Pincus Funds hold shares through their direct, wholly-owned subsidiary, WP XII Investments Cooperatief U.A. (&quot;WP XII Coop&quot;), which holds shares through its direct,wholly-owned subsidiary, WP XII Investments B.V. (&quot;WP XII BV&quot;).</footnote>
        <footnote id="F5">Warburg Pincus (Cayman) XII, L.P. (&quot;WP XII Cayman GP&quot;) is the general partner of each of the Warburg Pincus Funds. Warburg Pincus (Cayman) XII GP LLC (&quot;WP XII Cayman GP LLC&quot;) is the general partner of WP XII Cayman GP. Warburg Pincus Partners II (Cayman), L.P. (&quot;WPP II Cayman&quot;) is the sole member of WP XII Cayman GP LLC. WP Bermuda GP is the general partner of WPP II Cayman. WP LLC is the manager of each of the Warburg Pincus Funds.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F6">Each of the Warburg Pincus Funds, WP XII Coop, WP XII BV, WP XII Cayman GP, WP XII Cayman GP LLC, WPP II Cayman, WP Bermuda GP, and WP LLC are collectively referred to herein as the &quot;Warburg Pincus Entities.&quot; Charles R. Kaye and Joseph P. Landy are the sole Directors and Co-Chairmen of WP Bermuda GP and Managing Members and Co-Chief Executive Officers of WP LLC and may be deemed to control the Warburg Pincus Entities.</footnote>
    </footnotes>

    <ownerSignature>
        <signatureName>/s/ Eric Spindel, as Attorney-in-Fact</signatureName>
        <signatureDate>2019-01-24</signatureDate>
    </ownerSignature>
</ownershipDocument>
