<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ownershipDocument>

    <schemaVersion>X0306</schemaVersion>

    <documentType>4</documentType>

    <periodOfReport>2019-01-01</periodOfReport>

    <notSubjectToSection16>false</notSubjectToSection16>

    <issuer>
        <issuerCik>0001096385</issuerCik>
        <issuerName>VECTREN CORP</issuerName>
        <issuerTradingSymbol>VVC</issuerTradingSymbol>
    </issuer>

    <reportingOwner>
        <reportingOwnerId>
            <rptOwnerCik>0001584184</rptOwnerCik>
            <rptOwnerName>Hardwick M Susan</rptOwnerName>
        </reportingOwnerId>
        <reportingOwnerAddress>
            <rptOwnerStreet1>P.O. BOX 209</rptOwnerStreet1>
            <rptOwnerStreet2></rptOwnerStreet2>
            <rptOwnerCity>EVANSVILLE</rptOwnerCity>
            <rptOwnerState>IN</rptOwnerState>
            <rptOwnerZipCode>47708</rptOwnerZipCode>
            <rptOwnerStateDescription></rptOwnerStateDescription>
        </reportingOwnerAddress>
        <reportingOwnerRelationship>
            <isDirector>false</isDirector>
            <isOfficer>true</isOfficer>
            <isTenPercentOwner>false</isTenPercentOwner>
            <isOther>false</isOther>
            <officerTitle>EVP &amp; Chief Financial Officer</officerTitle>
            <otherText></otherText>
        </reportingOwnerRelationship>
    </reportingOwner>

    <nonDerivativeTable></nonDerivativeTable>

    <derivativeTable>
        <derivativeTransaction>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Phantom Stock</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <conversionOrExercisePrice>
                <value>0.00</value>
            </conversionOrExercisePrice>
            <transactionDate>
                <value>2019-01-01</value>
            </transactionDate>
            <deemedExecutionDate></deemedExecutionDate>
            <transactionCoding>
                <transactionFormType>4</transactionFormType>
                <transactionCode>A</transactionCode>
                <equitySwapInvolved>false</equitySwapInvolved>
            </transactionCoding>
            <transactionTimeliness></transactionTimeliness>
            <transactionAmounts>
                <transactionShares>
                    <value>8630.00</value>
                </transactionShares>
                <transactionPricePerShare>
                    <value>0.00</value>
                </transactionPricePerShare>
                <transactionAcquiredDisposedCode>
                    <value>A</value>
                </transactionAcquiredDisposedCode>
            </transactionAmounts>
            <exerciseDate>
                <footnoteId id="F1"/>
                <footnoteId id="F2"/>
                <footnoteId id="F3"/>
            </exerciseDate>
            <expirationDate>
                <footnoteId id="F1"/>
                <footnoteId id="F2"/>
                <footnoteId id="F3"/>
            </expirationDate>
            <underlyingSecurity>
                <underlyingSecurityTitle>
                    <value>Common Stock</value>
                </underlyingSecurityTitle>
                <underlyingSecurityShares>
                    <value>8630.00</value>
                </underlyingSecurityShares>
            </underlyingSecurity>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>8630.00</value>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>D</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </derivativeTransaction>
    </derivativeTable>

    <footnotes>
        <footnote id="F1">The stock unit award was granted pursuant to the Vectren Corporation At Risk Compensation Plan (Plan) and is subject to forfeiture as provided by the Plan and the Plan grant agreement. The lifting of restrictions and the application of the forfeiture provisions are dependent upon performance under pre-established metrics during a measuring period from January 1, 2019 through December 31, 2021 and subject to continued employment until certification of performance, except in limited circumstances as described in the Plan and the Plan grant agreement. Upon lifting of restrictions, the grantee shall be paid for each stock unit, in cash, a value determined by calculating the average of the closing price of Vectren's common stock for the three consecutive trading days immediately preceding ten calendar days before the certification of the performance results.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F2">Certification of the performance results is expected to be no later than March 31, 2022.  If the lifting of restrictions occurs prior to the performance certification date, the value of one share of Vectren's common stock on the date the restrictions lapse will be used to value each stock unit. At the time restrictions lift, if the grantee is not then in compliance with the company's share ownership guidelines, the value of each stock unit shall be paid to the grantee in one unrestricted share of Vectren's common stock. Dividends paid during the restriction period shall accrue as additional stock units and are subject to forfeiture. This acquisition was approved in accordance with Rule 16b-3.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F3">If the closing date of the previously announced merger transaction between Vectren Corporation and CenterPoint Energy, Inc. (CNP) occurs prior to December 31, 2021, then the Stock Unit Awards shall be cancelled and converted into a vested right to receive cash in an amount equal to (i) $72.00 multiplied by (ii) the number of Stock Unit Awards set forth herein, without any adjustment based on the Performance Criteria, multiplied by (iii) a fraction with a numerator equal to the number of days in the period beginning on the Grant Date and ending on the closing date of the transaction with CNP and a denominator equal to 1095, but in no event shall such fraction be greater than one.</footnote>
    </footnotes>

    <remarks></remarks>

    <ownerSignature>
        <signatureName>/s/Ronald E. Christian</signatureName>
        <signatureDate>2019-01-02</signatureDate>
    </ownerSignature>
</ownershipDocument>
