<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ownershipDocument>

    <schemaVersion>X0306</schemaVersion>

    <documentType>4</documentType>

    <periodOfReport>2019-01-04</periodOfReport>

    <notSubjectToSection16>0</notSubjectToSection16>

    <issuer>
        <issuerCik>0001158449</issuerCik>
        <issuerName>ADVANCE AUTO PARTS INC</issuerName>
        <issuerTradingSymbol>AAP</issuerTradingSymbol>
    </issuer>

    <reportingOwner>
        <reportingOwnerId>
            <rptOwnerCik>0001362697</rptOwnerCik>
            <rptOwnerName>Smith Jeffrey C</rptOwnerName>
        </reportingOwnerId>
        <reportingOwnerAddress>
            <rptOwnerStreet1>777 THIRD AVENUE, 18TH FLOOR</rptOwnerStreet1>
            <rptOwnerStreet2></rptOwnerStreet2>
            <rptOwnerCity>NEW YORK</rptOwnerCity>
            <rptOwnerState>NY</rptOwnerState>
            <rptOwnerZipCode>10017</rptOwnerZipCode>
            <rptOwnerStateDescription></rptOwnerStateDescription>
        </reportingOwnerAddress>
        <reportingOwnerRelationship>
            <isDirector>1</isDirector>
            <isOfficer>0</isOfficer>
            <isTenPercentOwner>0</isTenPercentOwner>
            <isOther>0</isOther>
            <officerTitle></officerTitle>
            <otherText></otherText>
        </reportingOwnerRelationship>
    </reportingOwner>

    <nonDerivativeTable>
        <nonDerivativeTransaction>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Common Stock, $0.0001 Par Value</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <transactionDate>
                <value>2019-01-04</value>
            </transactionDate>
            <deemedExecutionDate></deemedExecutionDate>
            <transactionCoding>
                <transactionFormType>4</transactionFormType>
                <transactionCode>A</transactionCode>
                <equitySwapInvolved>0</equitySwapInvolved>
            </transactionCoding>
            <transactionTimeliness></transactionTimeliness>
            <transactionAmounts>
                <transactionShares>
                    <value>2.214</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F1"/>
                </transactionShares>
                <transactionPricePerShare>
                    <value>158.81</value>
                </transactionPricePerShare>
                <transactionAcquiredDisposedCode>
                    <value>A</value>
                </transactionAcquiredDisposedCode>
            </transactionAmounts>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>5861.86</value>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>D</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeTransaction>
        <nonDerivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Common Stock, $0.0001 Par Value</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>1160354</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F9"/>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>By Starboard Value and Opportunity Master Fund Ltd</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F2"/>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeHolding>
        <nonDerivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Common Stock, $0.0001 Par Value</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>141771</value>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>By Starboard Value and Opportunity S LLC</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F3"/>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeHolding>
        <nonDerivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Common Stock, $0.0001 Par Value</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>81778</value>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>By Starboard Value and Opportunity C LP</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F4"/>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeHolding>
        <nonDerivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Common Stock, $0.0001 Par Value</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>1110079</value>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>By Starboard Leaders India LLC</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F5"/>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeHolding>
        <nonDerivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Common Stock, $0.0001 Par Value</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>281794</value>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>By Starboard T Fund LP</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F6"/>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeHolding>
        <nonDerivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Common Stock, $0.0001 Par Value</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>186206</value>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>By Starboard Leaders Select I LP</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F7"/>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeHolding>
        <nonDerivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Common Stock, $0.0001 Par Value</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>61071</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F9"/>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>By Starboard Value and Opportunity Master Fund L LP</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F8"/>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeHolding>
        <nonDerivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Common Stock, $0.0001 Par Value</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>151947</value>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>By Managed Account of Starboard Value LP</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F10"/>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeHolding>
    </nonDerivativeTable>

    <footnotes>
        <footnote id="F1">These shares of Issuer common stock were acquired pursuant to a dividend reinvestment feature of the Advance Auto Parts, Inc. Deferred Stock Unit Plan for Non-Employee Directors and Selected Executives.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F2">Securities owned directly by Starboard Value and Opportunity Master Fund Ltd (&quot;Starboard V&amp;O Fund&quot;). The Reporting Person, solely by virtue of his position as a member of the Management Committee of Starboard Value GP LLC (&quot;Starboard Value GP&quot;), the general partner of the investment manager of Starboard V&amp;O Fund, and as a member and member of the Management Committee of Starboard Principal Co GP LLC (&quot;Principal GP&quot;), the general partner of the member of Starboard Value GP, may be deemed to beneficially own the securities directly held by Starboard V&amp;O Fund for purposes of Section 16 of the Securities Exchange Act of 1934, as amended (&quot;Section 16&quot;). The Reporting Person expressly disclaims beneficial ownership of such securities except to the extent of his pecuniary interest therein.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F3">Securities owned directly by Starboard Value and Opportunity S LLC (&quot;Starboard S LLC&quot;). The Reporting Person, solely by virtue of his position as a member of the Management Committee of Starboard Value GP, the general partner of the manager of Starboard S LLC, and as a member and member of the Management Committee of Principal GP, the general partner of the member of Starboard Value GP, may be deemed to beneficially own the securities directly held by Starboard S LLC for purposes of Section 16. The Reporting Person expressly disclaims beneficial ownership of such securities except to the extent of his pecuniary interest therein.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F4">Securities owned directly by Starboard Value and Opportunity C LP (&quot;Starboard C LP&quot;). The Reporting Person, solely by virtue of his position as a member of the Management Committee of Starboard Value GP, the general partner of the investment manager of Starboard C LP, and as a member and member of the Management Committee of Principal GP, the general partner of the member of Starboard Value GP, may be deemed to beneficially own the securities directly held by Starboard C LP for purposes of Section 16. The Reporting Person expressly disclaims beneficial ownership of such securities except to the extent of his pecuniary interest therein.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F5">Securities owned directly by Starboard Leaders India LLC (&quot;Starboard India LLC&quot;). The Reporting Person, solely by virtue of his position as a member of the Management Committee of Starboard Value GP, the general partner of the investment manager of Starboard India LLC, and as a member and member of the Management Committee of Principal GP, the general partner of the member of Starboard Value GP, may be deemed to beneficially own the securities directly held by Starboard India LLC for purposes of Section 16. The Reporting Person expressly disclaims beneficial ownership of such securities except to the extent of his pecuniary interest therein.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F6">Securities owned directly by Starboard T Fund LP (&quot;Starboard T LP&quot;). The Reporting Person, solely by virtue of his position as a member of the Management Committee of Starboard Value GP, the general partner of the investment manager of Starboard T LP, and as a member and member of the Management Committee of Principal GP, the general partner of the member of Starboard Value GP, may be deemed to beneficially own the securities directly held by Starboard T LP for purposes of Section 16. The Reporting Person expressly disclaims beneficial ownership of such securities except to the extent of his pecuniary interest therein.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F7">Securities owned directly by Starboard Leaders Select I LP (&quot;Starboard Leaders Select I&quot;). The Reporting Person, solely by virtue of his position as a member of the Management Committee of Starboard Value GP, the general partner of the investment manager of Starboard Leaders Select I, and as a member and member of the Management Committee of Principal GP, the general partner of the member of Starboard Value GP, may be deemed to beneficially own the securities directly held by Starboard Leaders Select I for purposes of Section 16. The Reporting Person expressly disclaims beneficial ownership of such securities except to the extent of his pecuniary interest therein.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F8">Securities owned directly by Starboard Value and Opportunity Master Fund L LP (&quot;Starboard L LP&quot;). The Reporting Person, solely by virtue of his position as a member of the Management Committee of Starboard Value GP, the general partner of the investment manager of Starboard L LP, and as a member and member of the Management Committee of Principal GP, the general partner of the member of Starboard Value GP, may be deemed to beneficially own the securities directly held by Starboard L LP for purposes of Section 16. The Reporting Person expressly disclaims beneficial ownership of such securities except to the extent of his pecuniary interest therein.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F9">Starboard V&amp;O Fund transferred 61,071 shares of Common Stock held by it to Starboard L LP in a transaction exempt from Section 16, pursuant to Rule 16a-13 or otherwise.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F10">Securities held in an account managed by Starboard Value LP (the &quot;Managed Account&quot;). The Reporting Person, solely by virtue of his position as a member of the Management Committee of Starboard Value GP, the general partner of Starboard Value LP, and as a member and member of the Management Committee of Principal GP, the general partner of the member of Starboard Value GP, may be deemed to beneficially own the securities held in the Managed Account for purposes of Section 16. The Reporting Person expressly disclaims beneficial ownership of such securities except to the extent of his pecuniary interest therein.</footnote>
    </footnotes>

    <ownerSignature>
        <signatureName>/s/ Jeffrey C. Smith</signatureName>
        <signatureDate>2019-01-08</signatureDate>
    </ownerSignature>
</ownershipDocument>
