<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ownershipDocument>

    <schemaVersion>X0306</schemaVersion>

    <documentType>4</documentType>

    <periodOfReport>2019-01-20</periodOfReport>

    <notSubjectToSection16>0</notSubjectToSection16>

    <issuer>
        <issuerCik>0001176948</issuerCik>
        <issuerName>Ares Management Corp</issuerName>
        <issuerTradingSymbol>ARES</issuerTradingSymbol>
    </issuer>

    <reportingOwner>
        <reportingOwnerId>
            <rptOwnerCik>0001464431</rptOwnerCik>
            <rptOwnerName>McFerran Michael R</rptOwnerName>
        </reportingOwnerId>
        <reportingOwnerAddress>
            <rptOwnerStreet1>2000 AVENUE OF THE STARS</rptOwnerStreet1>
            <rptOwnerStreet2>12TH FLOOR</rptOwnerStreet2>
            <rptOwnerCity>LOS ANGELES</rptOwnerCity>
            <rptOwnerState>CA</rptOwnerState>
            <rptOwnerZipCode>90067</rptOwnerZipCode>
            <rptOwnerStateDescription></rptOwnerStateDescription>
        </reportingOwnerAddress>
        <reportingOwnerRelationship>
            <isDirector>0</isDirector>
            <isOfficer>1</isOfficer>
            <isTenPercentOwner>0</isTenPercentOwner>
            <isOther>0</isOther>
            <officerTitle>EVP, CFO &amp; COO</officerTitle>
        </reportingOwnerRelationship>
    </reportingOwner>

    <nonDerivativeTable>
        <nonDerivativeTransaction>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Class A Common Stock</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <transactionDate>
                <value>2019-01-20</value>
            </transactionDate>
            <transactionCoding>
                <transactionFormType>4</transactionFormType>
                <transactionCode>A</transactionCode>
                <equitySwapInvolved>0</equitySwapInvolved>
            </transactionCoding>
            <transactionTimeliness>
                <value></value>
            </transactionTimeliness>
            <transactionAmounts>
                <transactionShares>
                    <value>20650</value>
                </transactionShares>
                <transactionPricePerShare>
                    <value>0</value>
                </transactionPricePerShare>
                <transactionAcquiredDisposedCode>
                    <value>A</value>
                </transactionAcquiredDisposedCode>
            </transactionAmounts>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>629931</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F1"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F2"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F3"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F4"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F5"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F6"/>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>D</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeTransaction>
    </nonDerivativeTable>

    <footnotes>
        <footnote id="F1">Reflects a grant of 20,650 restricted units granted on January 20, 2019, each of which represents the right to receive one share of Class A Common Stock upon vesting. The restrictions on such units are scheduled to lapse in three equal installments on January 20, 2020, 2021 and 2022. Also includes 250,000 restricted units granted on November 1, 2018, each of which represents the right to receive one share of Class A Common Stock upon vesting. The restrictions on such units are scheduled to lapse in four equal installments on November 1, 2020, 2021, 2022 and 2023. Also includes 22,989 restricted units granted on March 23, 2018, each of which represents the right to receive one share of Class A Common Stock upon vesting. The restrictions on such units are scheduled to lapse in three equal installments on March 23, 2021, 2022 and 2023.(Continued in Footnote 2)</footnote>
        <footnote id="F2">Also includes 12,103 restricted units granted on January 20, 2018, each of which represents the right to receive one share of Class A Common Stock upon vesting. The restrictions on such units are scheduled to lapse in four equal installments on January 20, 2019, 2020, 2021 and 2022. In connection with the vesting on January 20, 2019, the reporting person received 1,987 shares of Class A Common Stock, with the remaining 1,039 shares of Class A Common Stock withheld to cover taxes on this transaction. Also includes 27,248 restricted units granted on March 23, 2017, each of which represents the right to receive one share of Class A Common Stock upon vesting. The restrictions on such units are scheduled to lapse in three equal installments on March 23, 2020, 2021 and 2022.(Continued in Footnote 3)</footnote>
        <footnote id="F3">Also includes 100,000 restricted units granted on January 31, 2017, each of which represents the right to receive one share of Class A Common Stock upon vesting. The restrictions on such units are scheduled to lapse on January 31, 2022. Also includes 11,462 restricted units granted on January 20, 2017, each of which represents the right to receive one share of Class A Common Stock upon vesting. The restrictions on such units are scheduled to lapse in four equal installments on January 20, 2018, 2019, 2020 and 2021. In connection with the vesting on January 20, 2018, the reporting person received 1,870 shares of Class A Common Stock, with the remaining 996 shares of Class A Common Stock withheld to cover taxes on this transaction.(Continued in Footnote 4)</footnote>
        <footnote id="F4">In connection with the vesting on January 20, 2019, the reporting person received 1,878 shares of Class A Common Stock, with the remaining 988 shares of Class A Common Stock withheld to cover taxes on this transaction. Also includes 100,000 restricted units granted on August 15, 2016, each of which represents the right to receive one share of Class A Common Stock upon vesting. The restrictions on such units are scheduled to lapse on August 15, 2021. Also includes 36,497 restricted units granted on March 23, 2016, each of which represents the right to receive one share of Class A Common Stock upon vesting. The restrictions on such units are scheduled to lapse in three equal installments on March 23, 2019, 2020 and 2021. Also includes 15,068 restricted units granted on January 20, 2016, each of which represents the right to receive one share of Class A Common Stock upon vesting.(Continued in Footnote 5)</footnote>
        <footnote id="F5">The restrictions on such units are scheduled to lapse in four equal installments on January 20, 2017, 2018, 2019 and 2020. In connection with the vesting on January 20, 2017, the reporting person received 2,151 shares of Class A Common Stock, with the remaining 1,616 shares of Class A Common Stock withheld to cover taxes on this transaction. In connection with the vesting on January 20, 2018, the reporting person received 2,250 shares of Class A Common Stock, with the remaining 1,517 shares of Class A Common Stock withheld to cover taxes on this transaction. In connection with the vesting on January 20, 2019, the reporting person received 2,230 shares of Class A Common Stock, with the remaining 1,537 shares of Class A Common Stock withheld to cover taxes on this transaction. Also includes 27,248 restricted units granted on March 23, 2015, each of which represents the right to receive one share of Class A Common Stock upon vesting.(Continued in Footnote 6)</footnote>
        <footnote id="F6">The restrictions on such units are scheduled to lapse in three equal installments on March 23, 2018, 2019 and 2020. In connection with the vesting on March 23, 2018, the reporting person received 5,942 shares of Class A Common Stock, with the remaining 3,141 shares of Class A Common Stock withheld to cover taxes on this transaction.</footnote>
    </footnotes>

    <ownerSignature>
        <signatureName>/s/ Michael R. McFerran</signatureName>
        <signatureDate>2019-01-23</signatureDate>
    </ownerSignature>
</ownershipDocument>
