<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ownershipDocument>

    <schemaVersion>X0306</schemaVersion>

    <documentType>4</documentType>

    <periodOfReport>2019-01-20</periodOfReport>

    <notSubjectToSection16>0</notSubjectToSection16>

    <issuer>
        <issuerCik>0001176948</issuerCik>
        <issuerName>Ares Management Corp</issuerName>
        <issuerTradingSymbol>ARES</issuerTradingSymbol>
    </issuer>

    <reportingOwner>
        <reportingOwnerId>
            <rptOwnerCik>0001267619</rptOwnerCik>
            <rptOwnerName>WEINER MICHAEL D</rptOwnerName>
        </reportingOwnerId>
        <reportingOwnerAddress>
            <rptOwnerStreet1>2000 AVENUE OF THE STARS</rptOwnerStreet1>
            <rptOwnerStreet2>12TH FLOOR</rptOwnerStreet2>
            <rptOwnerCity>LOS ANGELES</rptOwnerCity>
            <rptOwnerState>CA</rptOwnerState>
            <rptOwnerZipCode>90067</rptOwnerZipCode>
            <rptOwnerStateDescription></rptOwnerStateDescription>
        </reportingOwnerAddress>
        <reportingOwnerRelationship>
            <isDirector>0</isDirector>
            <isOfficer>1</isOfficer>
            <isTenPercentOwner>0</isTenPercentOwner>
            <isOther>0</isOther>
            <officerTitle>EVP, CLO &amp; Secretary</officerTitle>
        </reportingOwnerRelationship>
    </reportingOwner>

    <nonDerivativeTable>
        <nonDerivativeTransaction>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Class A Common Stock</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <transactionDate>
                <value>2019-01-20</value>
            </transactionDate>
            <transactionCoding>
                <transactionFormType>4</transactionFormType>
                <transactionCode>A</transactionCode>
                <equitySwapInvolved>0</equitySwapInvolved>
            </transactionCoding>
            <transactionTimeliness>
                <value></value>
            </transactionTimeliness>
            <transactionAmounts>
                <transactionShares>
                    <value>15075</value>
                </transactionShares>
                <transactionPricePerShare>
                    <value>0</value>
                </transactionPricePerShare>
                <transactionAcquiredDisposedCode>
                    <value>A</value>
                </transactionAcquiredDisposedCode>
            </transactionAmounts>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>99211</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F1"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F2"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F3"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F4"/>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>D</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeTransaction>
        <nonDerivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Class A Common Stock</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>154572</value>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>By Ares Owners Holdings L.P.</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F5"/>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeHolding>
    </nonDerivativeTable>

    <footnotes>
        <footnote id="F1">Reflects a grant of 15,075 restricted units granted on January 20, 2019, each of which represents the right to receive one share of Class A Common Stock upon vesting. The restrictions on such units are scheduled to lapse in three equal installments on January 20, 2020, 2021 and 2022. Also includes 8,299 restricted units granted on January 20, 2018, each of which represents the right to receive one share of Class A Common Stock upon vesting. The restrictions on such units are scheduled to lapse in four equal installments on January 20, 2019, 2020, 2021 and 2022. In connection with the vesting on January 20, 2019, the reporting person received 1,406 shares of Class A Common Stock, with the remaining 669 shares of Class A Common Stock withheld to cover taxes on this transaction.(Continued in Footnote 2)</footnote>
        <footnote id="F2">Also includes 25,000 restricted units granted on January 31, 2017, each of which represents the right to receive one share of Class A Common Stock upon vesting. The restrictions on such units are scheduled to lapse on January 31, 2022. Also includes 9,709 restricted units granted on January 20, 2017, each of which represents the right to receive one share of Class A Common Stock upon vesting. The restrictions on such units are scheduled to lapse in four equal installments on January 20, 2018, 2019, 2020 and 2021. In connection with the vesting on January 20, 2018, the reporting person received 1,621 shares of Class A Common Stock, with the remaining 807 shares of Class A Common Stock withheld to cover taxes on this transaction.(Continued in Footnote 3)</footnote>
        <footnote id="F3">In connection with the vesting on January 20, 2019, the reporting person received 1,644 shares of Class A Common Stock, with the remaining 783 shares of Class A Common Stock withheld to cover taxes on this transaction. Also includes 15,281 restricted units granted on January 20, 2016, each of which represents the right to receive one share of Class A Common Stock upon vesting. The restrictions on such units are scheduled to lapse in four equal installments on January 20, 2017, 2018, 2019 and 2020. In connection with the vesting on January 20, 2017, the reporting person received 2,474 shares of Class A Common Stock, with the remaining 1,347 shares of Class A Common Stock withheld to cover taxes on this transaction. In connection with the vesting on January 20, 2018, the reporting person received 2,550 shares of Class A Common Stock, with the remaining 1,270 shares of Class A Common Stock withheld to cover taxes on this transaction.(Continued in Footnote 4)</footnote>
        <footnote id="F4">In connection with the vesting on January 20, 2019, the reporting person received 2,560 shares of Class A Common Stock, with the remaining 1,260 shares of Class A Common Stock withheld to cover taxes on this transaction. Also includes 28,947 restricted units granted on May 1, 2014, each of which represents the right to receive one share of Class A Common Stock upon vesting. The restrictions are scheduled to lapse in three equal installments on May 1, 2017, 2018 and 2019. In connection with the vesting on May 1, 2017, the reporting person received 6,022 shares of Class A Common Stock, with the remaining 3,627 shares of Class A Common Stock withheld to cover taxes on this transaction. In connection with the vesting on May 1, 2018, the reporting person received 6,312 shares of Class A Common Stock, with the remaining 3,337 shares of Class A Common Stock withheld to cover taxes on this transaction.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F5">The reporting person or a vehicle controlled by him is a limited partner in Ares Owners Holdings L.P. (&quot;AOH&quot;), the direct holder of the shares of Class A Common Stock. The shares of Class A Common Stock indirectly held by the reporting person or the vehicle are the number of shares of Class A Common Stock that he or the vehicle has a right to receive as a limited partner in AOH.</footnote>
    </footnotes>

    <ownerSignature>
        <signatureName>/s/ Naseem Sagati Aghili, by power of attorney</signatureName>
        <signatureDate>2019-01-23</signatureDate>
    </ownerSignature>
</ownershipDocument>
