<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ownershipDocument>

    <schemaVersion>X0206</schemaVersion>

    <documentType>3</documentType>

    <periodOfReport>2018-12-18</periodOfReport>

    <noSecuritiesOwned>0</noSecuritiesOwned>

    <issuer>
        <issuerCik>0001468174</issuerCik>
        <issuerName>Hyatt Hotels Corp</issuerName>
        <issuerTradingSymbol>H</issuerTradingSymbol>
    </issuer>

    <reportingOwner>
        <reportingOwnerId>
            <rptOwnerCik>0001762015</rptOwnerCik>
            <rptOwnerName>DGC 2018 Trust</rptOwnerName>
        </reportingOwnerId>
        <reportingOwnerAddress>
            <rptOwnerStreet1>C/O HORTON TRUST COMPANY LLC</rptOwnerStreet1>
            <rptOwnerStreet2>444 W. LAKE, SUITE 3400</rptOwnerStreet2>
            <rptOwnerCity>CHICAGO</rptOwnerCity>
            <rptOwnerState>IL</rptOwnerState>
            <rptOwnerZipCode>60606</rptOwnerZipCode>
            <rptOwnerStateDescription></rptOwnerStateDescription>
        </reportingOwnerAddress>
        <reportingOwnerRelationship>
            <isDirector>0</isDirector>
            <isOfficer>0</isOfficer>
            <isTenPercentOwner>0</isTenPercentOwner>
            <isOther>1</isOther>
            <otherText>See Remarks</otherText>
        </reportingOwnerRelationship>
    </reportingOwner>

    <derivativeTable>
        <derivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Class B Common Stock</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <conversionOrExercisePrice>
                <value>0.00</value>
                <footnoteId id="F1"/>
            </conversionOrExercisePrice>
            <exerciseDate>
                <footnoteId id="F1"/>
            </exerciseDate>
            <expirationDate>
                <footnoteId id="F1"/>
            </expirationDate>
            <underlyingSecurity>
                <underlyingSecurityTitle>
                    <value>Class A Common Stock</value>
                </underlyingSecurityTitle>
                <underlyingSecurityShares>
                    <value>11685</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F2"/>
                </underlyingSecurityShares>
            </underlyingSecurity>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>D</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </derivativeHolding>
    </derivativeTable>

    <footnotes>
        <footnote id="F1">As provided in the Issuer's Amended and Restated Certificate of Incorporation, each share of Class B Common Stock is convertible at any time, at the option of the holder, into one share of Class A Common Stock.  In addition, each share of Class B Common Stock will convert automatically into one share of Class A Common Stock upon any transfer, whether or not for value, except for certain permitted transfers described in the Issuer's Amended and Restated Certificate of Incorporation.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F2">Represents shares previously owned by Don G.C. Trust #8.  No consideration was paid in connection with the receipt of shares of Class B Common Stock by the Reporting Person.  Such transfer of shares of Class B Common Stock to the Reporting Person constitutes a &quot;permitted transfer&quot; as defined under the Issuer's Amended and Restated Certificate of Incorporation.  Contemporaneous with such transfer, Horton Trust Company LLC, solely in its capacity as trustee of the Reporting Person, executed a joinder to, and thereby became subject to the provisions of, the Amended and Restated Global Hyatt Agreement.  Accordingly, immediately following the transfer, the shares will remain shares of Class B Common Stock.</footnote>
    </footnotes>

    <remarks>Member of 10% owner group.  Horton Trust Company LLC serves as trustee of the Reporting Person and has investment power over the shares beneficially owned by the Reporting Person.  The beneficiary of the Reporting Person does not have investment power over the shares of Class B Common Stock held by the Reporting Person.  In addition, the Reporting Person may be deemed to be a member of a group because the Reporting Person has agreed to certain voting agreements and limitations on transfers of shares of Class A Common Stock and Class B Common Stock.  The Reporting Person disclaims beneficial ownership of the securities reported herein except to the extent of its pecuniary interest therein.</remarks>

    <ownerSignature>
        <signatureName>/s/ Ronald D. Wray, Chief Operating Officer, Horton Trust Company LLC, as trustee</signatureName>
        <signatureDate>2018-12-19</signatureDate>
    </ownerSignature>
</ownershipDocument>
