<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ownershipDocument>

    <schemaVersion>X0306</schemaVersion>

    <documentType>4</documentType>

    <periodOfReport>2019-01-25</periodOfReport>

    <notSubjectToSection16>0</notSubjectToSection16>

    <issuer>
        <issuerCik>0001501364</issuerCik>
        <issuerName>United Financial Bancorp, Inc.</issuerName>
        <issuerTradingSymbol>UBNK</issuerTradingSymbol>
    </issuer>

    <reportingOwner>
        <reportingOwnerId>
            <rptOwnerCik>0001665250</rptOwnerCik>
            <rptOwnerName>Smith John James</rptOwnerName>
        </reportingOwnerId>
        <reportingOwnerAddress>
            <rptOwnerStreet1>C/O UNITED FINANCIAL BANCORP, INC.</rptOwnerStreet1>
            <rptOwnerStreet2>225 ASYLUM STREET</rptOwnerStreet2>
            <rptOwnerCity>HARTFORD</rptOwnerCity>
            <rptOwnerState>CT</rptOwnerState>
            <rptOwnerZipCode>06103</rptOwnerZipCode>
            <rptOwnerStateDescription></rptOwnerStateDescription>
        </reportingOwnerAddress>
        <reportingOwnerRelationship>
            <isDirector>0</isDirector>
            <isOfficer>1</isOfficer>
            <isTenPercentOwner>0</isTenPercentOwner>
            <isOther>0</isOther>
            <officerTitle>EVP</officerTitle>
            <otherText></otherText>
        </reportingOwnerRelationship>
    </reportingOwner>

    <nonDerivativeTable>
        <nonDerivativeTransaction>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Common Stock</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <transactionDate>
                <value>2019-01-25</value>
            </transactionDate>
            <transactionCoding>
                <transactionFormType>4</transactionFormType>
                <transactionCode>F</transactionCode>
                <equitySwapInvolved>0</equitySwapInvolved>
            </transactionCoding>
            <transactionAmounts>
                <transactionShares>
                    <value>2012</value>
                </transactionShares>
                <transactionPricePerShare>
                    <value>15.86</value>
                </transactionPricePerShare>
                <transactionAcquiredDisposedCode>
                    <value>D</value>
                </transactionAcquiredDisposedCode>
            </transactionAmounts>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>47321</value>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>D</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F1"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F2"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F3"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F4"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F5"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F6"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F7"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F8"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F9"/>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeTransaction>
        <nonDerivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Common Stock</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>123.60</value>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F10"/>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>By United Bank 401(k) Plan</value>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeHolding>
    </nonDerivativeTable>

    <derivativeTable></derivativeTable>

    <footnotes>
        <footnote id="F1">Includes 2,966 restricted shares granted pursuant to the United Financial Bancorp, Inc. 2015 Omnibus Stock Incentive Plan. The original grant of 3,832 shares vest in equal 33% increments over a three year period, the first 33% vesting on November 22, 2017 and the subsequent vesting on each on each annual anniversary of the grant date thereafter. The reported number of shares is net of 866 shares withheld by the Issuer for tax withholding purposes.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F2">Includes 9,290 restricted shares granted pursuant to the United Financial Bancorp, Inc. 2015 Omnibus Stock Incentive Plan. The original grant of 15,486 shares vest in equal 33% increments over a three year period, the first 33% vesting on January 19, 2017, and the subsequent vesting on each annual anniversary of his hire date thereafter. The reported number of shares is net of 6,196 shares withheld by the Issuer for tax withholding purposes.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F3">Includes 3,832 restricted stock shares granted pursuant to the United Financial Bancorp, Inc. 2015 Omnibus Stock Incentive Plan and cliff vest on December 31, 2019, if, and only if, United Financial Bancorp, Inc. meets certain performance goals.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F4">Includes 15,487 restricted shares granted pursuant to the United Financial Bancorp, Inc. 2015 Omnibus Stock Incentive Plan. The original grant of 15,487 shares cliff vest on the third anniversary of the hire date.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F5">Includes 3,590 restricted shares granted pursuant to the United Financial Bancorp, Inc. 2015 Omnibus Stock Incentive Plan. The original grant of 4,028 shares vest in equal 33% increments over a three year period, the first 33% vesting on November 22, 2018 and the subsequent vesting on each annual anniversary of the grant date thereafter. The reported number is net of 438 shares withheld by the Issuer for tax withholding purposes.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F6">Includes 3,584 restricted stock shares granted pursuant to the United Financial Bancorp, Inc. 2015 Omnibus Stock Incentive Plan and cliff vest on December 31, 2020, if, and only if, United Financial Bancorp, Inc. meets certain performance goals.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F7">Includes 4,286 restricted shares granted pursuant to the United Financial Bancorp, Inc. 2015 Omnibus Stock Incentive Plan. The original grant of 4,286 shares vest in equal 33% increments over a three year period, the first 33% vesting on November 19, 2019 and the subsequent vesting on each annual anniversary of the grant date thereafter.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F8">Includes 4,286 restricted stock shares granted pursuant to the United Financial Bancorp, Inc. 2015 Omnibus Stock Incentive Plan and cliff vest on December 31, 2021, if, and only if, United Financial Bancorp, Inc. meets certain performance goals.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F9">Transaction represents shares withheld by the Issuer for tax withholding purposes with respect to the vesting of Restricted Stock previously issued to the Reporting Person by the Issuer.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F10">Shares allocated to the account under the United Bank 401(k) Plan, of which all shares are vested</footnote>
    </footnotes>

    <remarks></remarks>

    <ownerSignature>
        <signatureName>/s/ Marliese L. Shaw by POA</signatureName>
        <signatureDate>2019-01-25</signatureDate>
    </ownerSignature>
</ownershipDocument>
