<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ownershipDocument>

    <schemaVersion>X0306</schemaVersion>

    <documentType>4</documentType>

    <periodOfReport>2019-01-14</periodOfReport>

    <notSubjectToSection16>true</notSubjectToSection16>

    <issuer>
        <issuerCik>0001544229</issuerCik>
        <issuerName>Engility Holdings, Inc.</issuerName>
        <issuerTradingSymbol>EGL</issuerTradingSymbol>
    </issuer>

    <reportingOwner>
        <reportingOwnerId>
            <rptOwnerCik>0001193340</rptOwnerCik>
            <rptOwnerName>DENNING STEVEN A</rptOwnerName>
        </reportingOwnerId>
        <reportingOwnerAddress>
            <rptOwnerStreet1>C/O GENERAL ATLANTIC SERVICE  COMPANY LP</rptOwnerStreet1>
            <rptOwnerStreet2>55 EAST 52ND STREET, 33RD FLOOR</rptOwnerStreet2>
            <rptOwnerCity>NEW YORK</rptOwnerCity>
            <rptOwnerState>NY</rptOwnerState>
            <rptOwnerZipCode>10055</rptOwnerZipCode>
            <rptOwnerStateDescription></rptOwnerStateDescription>
        </reportingOwnerAddress>
        <reportingOwnerRelationship>
            <isDirector>true</isDirector>
            <isTenPercentOwner>true</isTenPercentOwner>
        </reportingOwnerRelationship>
    </reportingOwner>

    <nonDerivativeTable>
        <nonDerivativeTransaction>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Common Stock</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <transactionDate>
                <value>2019-01-14</value>
            </transactionDate>
            <transactionCoding>
                <transactionFormType>4</transactionFormType>
                <transactionCode>D</transactionCode>
                <equitySwapInvolved>0</equitySwapInvolved>
            </transactionCoding>
            <transactionAmounts>
                <transactionShares>
                    <value>8960446</value>
                </transactionShares>
                <transactionPricePerShare>
                    <footnoteId id="F1"/>
                </transactionPricePerShare>
                <transactionAcquiredDisposedCode>
                    <value>D</value>
                </transactionAcquiredDisposedCode>
            </transactionAmounts>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>0</value>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>See footnotes</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F2"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F3"/>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeTransaction>
    </nonDerivativeTable>

    <footnotes>
        <footnote id="F1">Pursuant to the terms of the Agreement and Plan of Merger (the &quot;Merger Agreement&quot;), dated as of September 9, 2018, among Engility Holdings, Inc. (the &quot;Company&quot;), Science Applications International Corporation (&quot;SAIC&quot;) and Raptors Merger Sub, Inc. (&quot;Merger Sub&quot;), a wholly owned subsidiary of SAIC, each share of the Company's common stock owned by the reporting person immediately prior to the effective time (the &quot;Effective Time&quot;) of the merger of Merger Sub with and into the Company (the &quot;merger&quot;), with the Company surviving the merger as a wholly owned subsidiary of SAIC, was, upon the Effective Time, converted into the right to receive 0.450 shares of common stock of SAIC, with cash in lieu of fractional shares.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F2">By Birch Partners, LP (now New Birch Partners, LP) (&quot;Birch Partners&quot;).  Birch Partners directly held all of the shares of common stock of the Company reported herein (the &quot;Shares&quot;). Birch GP, LLC was the general partner of Birch Partners. The members of Birch GP, LLC were General Atlantic Partners 85, L.P., a Delaware limited partnership (&quot;GAP 85&quot;), and KKR 2006 Fund L.P. The limited partners of Birch Partners include GAP 85, GAP Coinvestments III, LLC, a Delaware limited liability company (&quot;GAPCO III&quot;), GAP Coinvestments IV, LLC, a Delaware limited liability company (&quot;GAPCO IV&quot;), GAP Coinvestments CDA, L.P., a Delaware limited partnership (&quot;GAPCO CDA&quot;), and GAPCO GmbH &amp; Co., KG, a German limited partnership (&quot;KG&quot; and, together with GAP 85, GAPCO III, GAPCO IV and GAPCO CDA, the &quot;GA Funds&quot;), as well as other investors. Collectively, the GA Funds may be deemed to have had an indirect beneficial interest in 8,960,446 Shares previously held by Birch Partners.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F3">Mr. Denning is the Chairman and a Managing Director of General Atlantic LLC (&quot;GA LLC&quot;). GA LLC is the general partner of General Atlantic GenPar, L.P., a Delaware limited partnership, which is the general partner of GAP 85. GA LLC is also the managing member of GAPCO III and GAPCO IV, and the general partner of GAPCO CDA. In addition, the managing directors of GA LLC control the voting and investment decisions of GAPCO Management GmbH, a German corporation, which is the general partner of KG. Mr. Denning disclaims beneficial ownership of these securities except to the extent of his pecuniary interest therein, and the inclusion of these securities in this report shall not be deemed an admission of beneficial ownership of such securities for purposes of Section 16 or for any other purposes.</footnote>
    </footnotes>

    <remarks>The reporting person described in the notes above may be deemed to be a member of a &quot;group&quot; for purposes of the Securities Exchange Act of 1934. The reporting person disclaims beneficial ownership of any securities deemed to be owned by the group that are not directly owned by the reporting person. In addition, the reporting person described in the notes above may be deemed to be a member of a &quot;group&quot; for purposes of the Securities Exchange Act of 1934 with other limited partners of Birch Partners or other members of Birch GP, LLC. This report shall not be deemed an admission that the reporting person is a member of a group or the beneficial owner of any securities not directly owned by the reporting person.</remarks>

    <ownerSignature>
        <signatureName>/s/ Jon Brooks as Attorney-in-Fact</signatureName>
        <signatureDate>2019-01-14</signatureDate>
    </ownerSignature>
</ownershipDocument>
