<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ownershipDocument>

    <schemaVersion>X0306</schemaVersion>

    <documentType>4</documentType>

    <periodOfReport>2019-01-02</periodOfReport>

    <notSubjectToSection16>0</notSubjectToSection16>

    <issuer>
        <issuerCik>0001567683</issuerCik>
        <issuerName>Clearway Energy, Inc.</issuerName>
        <issuerTradingSymbol>CWEN</issuerTradingSymbol>
    </issuer>

    <reportingOwner>
        <reportingOwnerId>
            <rptOwnerCik>0001685648</rptOwnerCik>
            <rptOwnerName>Plotkin Chad</rptOwnerName>
        </reportingOwnerId>
        <reportingOwnerAddress>
            <rptOwnerStreet1>CLEARWAY ENERGY, INC.</rptOwnerStreet1>
            <rptOwnerStreet2>300 CARNEGIE CENTER, SUITE 300</rptOwnerStreet2>
            <rptOwnerCity>PRINCETON</rptOwnerCity>
            <rptOwnerState>NJ</rptOwnerState>
            <rptOwnerZipCode>08540</rptOwnerZipCode>
            <rptOwnerStateDescription></rptOwnerStateDescription>
        </reportingOwnerAddress>
        <reportingOwnerRelationship>
            <isDirector>0</isDirector>
            <isOfficer>1</isOfficer>
            <isTenPercentOwner>0</isTenPercentOwner>
            <isOther>0</isOther>
            <officerTitle>SVP and CFO</officerTitle>
            <otherText></otherText>
        </reportingOwnerRelationship>
    </reportingOwner>

    <nonDerivativeTable>
        <nonDerivativeTransaction>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Class C Common Stock, par value $.01 per share</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <transactionDate>
                <value>2019-01-02</value>
            </transactionDate>
            <transactionCoding>
                <transactionFormType>4</transactionFormType>
                <transactionCode>F</transactionCode>
                <equitySwapInvolved>0</equitySwapInvolved>
            </transactionCoding>
            <transactionAmounts>
                <transactionShares>
                    <value>1104</value>
                </transactionShares>
                <transactionPricePerShare>
                    <footnoteId id="F1"/>
                </transactionPricePerShare>
                <transactionAcquiredDisposedCode>
                    <value>D</value>
                </transactionAcquiredDisposedCode>
            </transactionAmounts>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>25674</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F2"/>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>D</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeTransaction>
        <nonDerivativeTransaction>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Class C Common Stock, par value $.01 per share</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <transactionDate>
                <value>2019-01-02</value>
            </transactionDate>
            <transactionCoding>
                <transactionFormType>4</transactionFormType>
                <transactionCode>A</transactionCode>
                <equitySwapInvolved>0</equitySwapInvolved>
            </transactionCoding>
            <transactionAmounts>
                <transactionShares>
                    <value>9114</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F3"/>
                </transactionShares>
                <transactionPricePerShare>
                    <footnoteId id="F4"/>
                </transactionPricePerShare>
                <transactionAcquiredDisposedCode>
                    <value>A</value>
                </transactionAcquiredDisposedCode>
            </transactionAmounts>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>34788</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F5"/>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>D</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeTransaction>
        <nonDerivativeTransaction>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Class C Common Stock, par value $.01 per share</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <transactionDate>
                <value>2019-01-03</value>
            </transactionDate>
            <transactionCoding>
                <transactionFormType>4</transactionFormType>
                <transactionCode>F</transactionCode>
                <equitySwapInvolved>0</equitySwapInvolved>
            </transactionCoding>
            <transactionAmounts>
                <transactionShares>
                    <value>1440</value>
                </transactionShares>
                <transactionPricePerShare>
                    <footnoteId id="F6"/>
                </transactionPricePerShare>
                <transactionAcquiredDisposedCode>
                    <value>D</value>
                </transactionAcquiredDisposedCode>
            </transactionAmounts>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>33348</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F7"/>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>D</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeTransaction>
    </nonDerivativeTable>

    <derivativeTable>
        <derivativeTransaction>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Relative Performance Stock Units</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <conversionOrExercisePrice>
                <footnoteId id="F8"/>
            </conversionOrExercisePrice>
            <transactionDate>
                <value>2019-01-02</value>
            </transactionDate>
            <transactionCoding>
                <transactionFormType>4</transactionFormType>
                <transactionCode>A</transactionCode>
                <equitySwapInvolved>0</equitySwapInvolved>
            </transactionCoding>
            <transactionAmounts>
                <transactionShares>
                    <value>17001</value>
                </transactionShares>
                <transactionPricePerShare>
                    <value>0</value>
                </transactionPricePerShare>
                <transactionAcquiredDisposedCode>
                    <value>A</value>
                </transactionAcquiredDisposedCode>
            </transactionAmounts>
            <exerciseDate>
                <value>2022-01-02</value>
            </exerciseDate>
            <expirationDate>
                <value>2022-01-02</value>
            </expirationDate>
            <underlyingSecurity>
                <underlyingSecurityTitle>
                    <value>Class C Common Stock, par value $.01 per share</value>
                </underlyingSecurityTitle>
                <underlyingSecurityShares>
                    <value>25501</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F9"/>
                </underlyingSecurityShares>
            </underlyingSecurity>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>17001</value>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>D</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </derivativeTransaction>
    </derivativeTable>

    <footnotes>
        <footnote id="F1">On January 2, 2018, Mr. Plotkin was issued 5,954 Restricted Stock Units (&quot;RSUs&quot;) by Clearway Energy, Inc. (f/k/a NRG Yield, Inc.) under Clearway Energy Inc.'s Amended and Restated 2013 Equity Incentive Plan (the &quot;LTIP&quot;). These RSUs vest ratably over a three-year period beginning on the first anniversary of the date of the grant. Each RSU is equivalent in value to one share of Class C Common Stock of Clearway Energy Inc., par value $.01 per share. On January 2, 2019, 1,982 shares vested. Mr. Plotkin elected to satisfy his tax obligation upon the exchange of common stock for RSUs having a value on the date of the exchange equal to the withholding obligation. This form reflects the surrender of 1,104 shares of Class C Common Stock to satisfy the grantee's tax withholding obligation.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F2">In connection with the vesting of the RSUs described above, 142 DERs converted to Class C Common Stock, resulting in the reporting person holding 3,947 dividend equivalent rights that may only be settled in Class C Common Stock. Dividend equivalent rights accrue on the reporting person's restricted stock, which become exercisable proportionately with the restricted stock units to which they relate and may only be settled in Clearway Energy, Inc. Class C Common Stock. Each dividend equivalent right is the economic equivalent of one share of Clearway Energy, Inc. Class C Common Stock.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F3">Represents RSUs issued to Mr. Plotkin under the LTIP.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F4">Each RSU is equivalent in value to one share of Clearway Energy, Inc.'s Class C Common Stock, par value $.01 per share.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F5">The Reporting Person will receive from Clearway Energy, Inc. one such share of Class C Common Stock for each RSU that will vest ratably over a three-year period beginning on the first anniversary ofthe date of the grant.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F6">On January 3, 2017, Mr. Plotkin was issued 7,357 Restricted Stock Units (&quot;RSUs&quot;) by Clearway Energy, Inc. (f/k/a NRG Yield, Inc.) under the LTIP. These RSUs vest ratably over a three-year period beginning on the first anniversary of the date of the grant. Each RSU is equivalent in value to one share of Class C Common Stock of Clearway Energy Inc., par value $.01 per share. On January 3, 2019, 2,450 shares vested. Mr. Plotkin elected to satisfy his tax obligation upon the exchange of common stock for RSUs having a value on the date of the exchange equal to the withholding obligation. This form reflects the surrender of 1,440 shares of Class C Common Stock to satisfy the grantee's tax withholding obligation.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F7">In connection with the vesting of the RSUs described above, 338 DERs converted to Class C Common Stock, resulting in the reporting person holding 3,609 dividend equivalent rights that may only be settled in Class C Common Stock. Dividend equivalent rights accrue on the reporting person's restricted stock, which become exercisable proportionately with the restricted stock units to which they relate and may only be settled in Clearway Energy, Inc. Class C Common Stock. Each dividend equivalent right is the economic equivalent of one share of Clearway Energy, Inc. Class C Common Stock.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F8">The Reporting Person was issued 17,001 Relative Performance Stock Units (&quot;RPSUs&quot;) by Clearway Energy, Inc. under the LTIP on January 2, 2019. The RPSUs will convert to shares of ClearwayEnergy, Inc. Class C Common Stock on January 2, 2022 only in the event the Company has achieved a certain level of total shareholder return (&quot;TSR&quot;) relative to the Peer Group (defined below) over a three-year performance period. The number of shares of Common Stock that the Reporting Person may receive is interpolated for TSR falling between Threshold, Target, and Maximum levels as described below.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F9">Reporting Person will receive (i) a maximum of shares of 25,501 Class C Common Stock if Company's TSR is ranked at or above the 75th percentile relative to a peer group of companies approved by the Company's Compensation Committee (the &quot;Peer Group&quot;) for the performance period (&quot;Maximum&quot;); (ii) 17,001 shares of Class C Common Stock if Company's TSR is ranked at the 50th percentile relative to the Peer Group for the performance period (the &quot;Target&quot;); provided, however, if TSR is less than negative twenty percent (-20%), the Company's TSR must be ranked at the 60th percentile relative to the Peer Group for the performance period to receive the Target award; or (iii) 4,250 shares of Common Stock if Company's TSR is ranked at the 25th percentile relative to the Peer Group for the performance period (the &quot;Threshold&quot;). The Reporting Person will not receive any shares of Common Stock if Company's TSR is below the 25th percentile.</footnote>
    </footnotes>

    <ownerSignature>
        <signatureName>/s/ Michael A. Brown, by Power of Attorney</signatureName>
        <signatureDate>2019-01-04</signatureDate>
    </ownerSignature>
</ownershipDocument>
