<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ownershipDocument>

    <schemaVersion>X0206</schemaVersion>

    <documentType>3</documentType>

    <periodOfReport>2018-12-26</periodOfReport>

    <noSecuritiesOwned>0</noSecuritiesOwned>

    <issuer>
        <issuerCik>0001571996</issuerCik>
        <issuerName>Dell Technologies Inc</issuerName>
        <issuerTradingSymbol>DELL</issuerTradingSymbol>
    </issuer>

    <reportingOwner>
        <reportingOwnerId>
            <rptOwnerCik>0001021944</rptOwnerCik>
            <rptOwnerName>Temasek Holdings (Private) Ltd</rptOwnerName>
        </reportingOwnerId>
        <reportingOwnerAddress>
            <rptOwnerStreet1>60B ORCHARD ROAD #06-18 TOWER 2</rptOwnerStreet1>
            <rptOwnerStreet2>THE ATRIUM@ORCHARD</rptOwnerStreet2>
            <rptOwnerCity>SINGAPORE</rptOwnerCity>
            <rptOwnerState>U0</rptOwnerState>
            <rptOwnerZipCode>238891</rptOwnerZipCode>
            <rptOwnerStateDescription>SINGAPORE</rptOwnerStateDescription>
        </reportingOwnerAddress>
        <reportingOwnerRelationship>
            <isTenPercentOwner>true</isTenPercentOwner>
        </reportingOwnerRelationship>
    </reportingOwner>

    <nonDerivativeTable>
        <nonDerivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Class C Common Stock</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>18181818</value>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>See Footnote</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F1"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F2"/>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeHolding>
    </nonDerivativeTable>

    <footnotes>
        <footnote id="F1">The shares of Class C Common Stock are directly held by Venezio Investments Pte. Ltd., which is a direct wholly-owned subsidiary of Napier Investments Pte. Ltd.  Napier Investments Pte. Ltd. is a direct wholly-owned subsidiary of Tembusu Capital Pte. Ltd., which in turn is a direct wholly-owned subsidiary of Temasek Holdings (Private) Limited.  Napier Investments Pte. Ltd., Tembusu Capital Pte. Ltd. and Temasek Holdings (Private) Limited may therefore be deemed to have or share beneficial ownership of the securities held by Venezio Investments Pte. Ltd.  Each such person disclaims beneficial ownership of such shares except to the extent of its pecuniary interest therein, and the inclusion of these securities in this report shall not be deemed an admission of beneficial ownership of the reported securities for purposes of Section 16 or for any other purposes.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F2">Venezio Investment Pte. Ltd. acquired the Class C Common Stock pursuant to a Common Stock Purchase Agreement by and between Denali Holding Inc. and Venezio Investment Pte. Ltd., dated as of October 12, 2015.  The reporting persons are making this filing as a result of the registration of the Class C Common Stock by Dell Technologies Inc. as of the date hereof in connection with the transactions contemplated by the Agreement and Plan of Merger, dated July 1, 2018 (as amended from time to time), between the Issuer and Teton Merger Sub Inc.</footnote>
    </footnotes>

    <ownerSignature>
        <signatureName>/s/ Gregory Tan, Authorised Signatory, Temasek Holdings (Private) Limited</signatureName>
        <signatureDate>2018-12-26</signatureDate>
    </ownerSignature>
</ownershipDocument>
