<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ownershipDocument>

    <schemaVersion>X0306</schemaVersion>

    <documentType>4</documentType>

    <periodOfReport>2019-01-02</periodOfReport>

    <notSubjectToSection16>0</notSubjectToSection16>

    <issuer>
        <issuerCik>0001623925</issuerCik>
        <issuerName>Antero Midstream GP LP</issuerName>
        <issuerTradingSymbol>AMGP</issuerTradingSymbol>
    </issuer>

    <reportingOwner>
        <reportingOwnerId>
            <rptOwnerCik>0001239315</rptOwnerCik>
            <rptOwnerName>KAGAN PETER</rptOwnerName>
        </reportingOwnerId>
        <reportingOwnerAddress>
            <rptOwnerStreet1>C/O WARBURG PINCUS &amp; CO.</rptOwnerStreet1>
            <rptOwnerStreet2>450 LEXINGTON AVENUE</rptOwnerStreet2>
            <rptOwnerCity>NEW YORK</rptOwnerCity>
            <rptOwnerState>NY</rptOwnerState>
            <rptOwnerZipCode>10017</rptOwnerZipCode>
            <rptOwnerStateDescription></rptOwnerStateDescription>
        </reportingOwnerAddress>
        <reportingOwnerRelationship>
            <isDirector>1</isDirector>
            <isOfficer>0</isOfficer>
            <isTenPercentOwner>0</isTenPercentOwner>
            <isOther>0</isOther>
        </reportingOwnerRelationship>
    </reportingOwner>

    <nonDerivativeTable>
        <nonDerivativeTransaction>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Common shares representing limited partner interests</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <transactionDate>
                <value>2019-01-02</value>
            </transactionDate>
            <transactionCoding>
                <transactionFormType>4</transactionFormType>
                <transactionCode>A</transactionCode>
                <equitySwapInvolved>0</equitySwapInvolved>
            </transactionCoding>
            <transactionTimeliness>
                <value></value>
            </transactionTimeliness>
            <transactionAmounts>
                <transactionShares>
                    <value>3731</value>
                </transactionShares>
                <transactionPricePerShare>
                    <value>0.0000</value>
                </transactionPricePerShare>
                <transactionAcquiredDisposedCode>
                    <value>A</value>
                </transactionAcquiredDisposedCode>
            </transactionAmounts>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>15812</value>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>D</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeTransaction>
        <nonDerivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Common shares representing limited partner interests</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>55109589</value>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>See footnotes</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F1"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F2"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F3"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F4"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F5"/>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeHolding>
    </nonDerivativeTable>

    <footnotes>
        <footnote id="F1">The Reporting Person is a Partner of Warburg Pincus &amp; Co., a New York general partnership (&quot;WP&quot;), and a Member and Managing Director of Warburg Pincus LLC, a New York limited liability company (&quot;WP LLC&quot;). The Warburg Pincus Entities (as defined below) collectively own 55,109,589 Common Shares, as of the date hereof.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F2">All Common Shares indicated as indirectly owned by the Reporting Person are included because of his affiliation with the Warburg Pincus Entities, due to which Mr. Kagan may be deemed to have an indirect pecuniary interest (within the meaning of Rule 16a-1 under the Securities and Exchange Act of 1934, as amended) in an indeterminate portion of the Common Shares owned by the Warburg Pincus Entities. Mr. Kagan disclaims beneficial ownership of all Common Shares attributable to the Warburg Pincus Entities except to the extent of his direct pecuniary interest therein.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F3">The Warburg Pincus funds are Warburg Pincus Private Equity VIII, L.P., a Delaware limited partnership (&quot;WP VIII&quot;, and together with its two affiliated partnerships, Warburg Pincus Netherlands Private Equity VIII C.V. I, a company formed under the laws of the Netherlands (&quot;WP VIII CV I&quot;), and WP-WPVIII Investors, L.P., a Delaware limited partnership (&quot;WP-WPVIII Investors&quot;), collectively, the &quot;WP VIII Funds&quot;), Warburg Pincus Private Equity X O&amp;G, L.P., a Delaware limited partnership (&quot;WP X O&amp;G&quot;), and Warburg Pincus X Partners, L.P., a Delaware limited partnership (&quot;WP X Partners&quot;, and together with WP X O&amp;G, the &quot;WP X O&amp;G Funds&quot;). WP-WPVIII Investors GP L.P., a Delaware limited partnership (&quot;WP-WPVIII GP&quot;), is the general partner of WP-WPVIII Investors. Warburg Pincus X, L.P., a Delaware limited partnership (&quot;WP X GP&quot;), is the general partner of each of the WP X O&amp;G Funds.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F4">Warburg Pincus X GP L.P., a Delaware limited partnership (&quot;WP X GP LP&quot;), is the general partner of WP X GP. WPP GP LLC, a Delaware limited liability company (&quot;WPP GP&quot;), is the general partner of WP-WPVIII GP and WP X GP LP. Warburg Pincus Partners, L.P., a Delaware limited partnership (&quot;WP Partners&quot;), is (i) the managing member of WPP GP, and (ii) the general partner of WP VIII and WP VIII CV I. Warburg Pincus Partners GP LLC, a Delaware limited liability company (&quot;WP Partners GP&quot;), is the general partner of WP Partners. WP is the managing member of WP Partners GP. WP LLC is the manager of each of the WP VIII Funds and the WP X O&amp;G Funds.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F5">Each of the WP VIII Funds, the WP X O&amp;G Funds, WP-WPVIII GP, WP X GP, WP X GP LP, WPP GP, WP Partners, WP Partners GP, WP and WP LLC are collectively referred to herein as the &quot;Warburg Pincus Entities.&quot;</footnote>
    </footnotes>

    <remarks>The Issuer is a Delaware limited partnership, managed by the directors and officers of its general partner, AMGP GP LLC, a Delaware limited liability company (''AMGP GP'').  Mr. Kagan is a director of AMGP GP. ***The Power of Attorney given by Mr. Kagan was previously filed with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission on October 12, 2016 as an exhibit to the Form 4 filed by Mr. Kagan with respect to the Antero Resources Corporation and is hereby incorporated by reference.</remarks>

    <ownerSignature>
        <signatureName>/s/ Robert B. Knauss, By: Robert B. Knauss, Attorney-In-Fact for Peter R. Kagan***</signatureName>
        <signatureDate>2019-01-04</signatureDate>
    </ownerSignature>
</ownershipDocument>
