<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ownershipDocument>

    <schemaVersion>X0306</schemaVersion>

    <documentType>4</documentType>

    <periodOfReport>2019-01-02</periodOfReport>

    <issuer>
        <issuerCik>0001692412</issuerCik>
        <issuerName>Playa Hotels &amp; Resorts N.V.</issuerName>
        <issuerTradingSymbol>PLYA</issuerTradingSymbol>
    </issuer>

    <reportingOwner>
        <reportingOwnerId>
            <rptOwnerCik>0001245637</rptOwnerCik>
            <rptOwnerName>FRIED RICHARD B</rptOwnerName>
        </reportingOwnerId>
        <reportingOwnerAddress>
            <rptOwnerStreet1>C/O FARALLON CAPITAL MANAGEMENT, L.L.C.</rptOwnerStreet1>
            <rptOwnerStreet2>ONE MARITIME PLAZA, SUITE 2100</rptOwnerStreet2>
            <rptOwnerCity>SAN FRANCISCO</rptOwnerCity>
            <rptOwnerState>CA</rptOwnerState>
            <rptOwnerZipCode>94111</rptOwnerZipCode>
            <rptOwnerStateDescription></rptOwnerStateDescription>
        </reportingOwnerAddress>
        <reportingOwnerRelationship>
            <isDirector>true</isDirector>
            <isOfficer>false</isOfficer>
            <isTenPercentOwner>true</isTenPercentOwner>
            <isOther>true</isOther>
            <officerTitle></officerTitle>
            <otherText>Member of Group Owning 10%</otherText>
        </reportingOwnerRelationship>
    </reportingOwner>

    <nonDerivativeTable>
        <nonDerivativeTransaction>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Ordinary Shares, par value EUR 0.10 per share</value>
                <footnoteId id="F1"/>
            </securityTitle>
            <transactionDate>
                <value>2019-01-02</value>
            </transactionDate>
            <deemedExecutionDate></deemedExecutionDate>
            <transactionCoding>
                <transactionFormType>4</transactionFormType>
                <transactionCode>A</transactionCode>
                <equitySwapInvolved>false</equitySwapInvolved>
            </transactionCoding>
            <transactionTimeliness></transactionTimeliness>
            <transactionAmounts>
                <transactionShares>
                    <value>10730</value>
                </transactionShares>
                <transactionPricePerShare>
                    <value>0</value>
                </transactionPricePerShare>
                <transactionAcquiredDisposedCode>
                    <value>A</value>
                </transactionAcquiredDisposedCode>
            </transactionAmounts>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>17687</value>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>D</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeTransaction>
        <nonDerivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Ordinary Shares, par value EUR 0.10 per share</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>30606930</value>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>See Footnotes</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F2"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F3"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F4"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F5"/>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeHolding>
    </nonDerivativeTable>

    <derivativeTable></derivativeTable>

    <footnotes>
        <footnote id="F1">On January 2, 2019, pursuant to the Issuer's 2017 Omnibus Incentive Plan, the Issuer awarded 10,730 Ordinary Shares to Richard B. Fried (&quot;Fried&quot;), a director of the Issuer.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F2">The amount of securities shown in this row is owned directly by Cabana Investors B.V. (&quot;Cabana&quot;) and Playa Four Pack, L.L.C. (&quot;Four Pack&quot; and, together with Cabana, the &quot;Farallon SPVs&quot;). All of such securities were previously reported by the Farallon SPVs, Farallon Partners, L.L.C. (the &quot;Farallon General Partner&quot;) and related individuals on Forms 4 filed on June 21, 2017 (collectively, the &quot;Prior Filings&quot;). There have been no transactions in such securities by any such entities or individuals since the filing of the Prior Filings.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F3">The Farallon General Partner, as (i) the general partner of each of the investment funds that are the members of Four Pack and (ii) the general partner of each of the investment funds that are the shareholders of the entity that is the indirect sole owner of Cabana, may be deemed to be a beneficial owner of the Issuer's securities held by the Farallon SPVs. The Farallon General Partner disclaims any beneficial ownership of any of the Issuer's securities reported or referred to herein or in the Prior Filings for purposes of Section 16 of the Securities Exchange Act of 1934, as amended (the &quot;'34 Act&quot;), or otherwise, except as to securities representing its pro rata interest in, and interest in the profits of, the Farallon SPVs.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F4">Fried, as a managing member of the Farallon General Partner with the power to exercise investment discretion, may be deemed to be a beneficial owner of the Issuer's securities held by the Farallon SPVs. Fried disclaims any beneficial ownership of any of the Issuer's securities reported or referred to in this row or in the Prior Filings for purposes of Section 16 of the '34 Act or otherwise, except to the extent of his pecuniary interest, if any. Each of the individuals identified in the Prior Filings disclaims any beneficial ownership of any of the Issuer's securities reported or referred to herein or in the Prior Filings for purposes of Section 16 of the '34 Act or otherwise, except to the extent of his or her pecuniary interest, if any.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F5">Fried, the Farallon SPVs, the Farallon General Partner and each of the individuals identified in the Prior Filings as a managing member or senior managing member of the Farallon General Partner with the power to exercise investment discretion, may be deemed members of a group holding equity securities of the Issuer. The filing of this Form 4 and any statements included herein shall not be deemed to be an admission that such entities and individuals are members of such a group.</footnote>
    </footnotes>

    <remarks></remarks>

    <ownerSignature>
        <signatureName>/s/ Richard B. Fried</signatureName>
        <signatureDate>2019-01-04</signatureDate>
    </ownerSignature>
</ownershipDocument>
