<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ownershipDocument>

    <schemaVersion>X0306</schemaVersion>

    <documentType>4</documentType>

    <periodOfReport>2018-01-31</periodOfReport>

    <notSubjectToSection16>1</notSubjectToSection16>

    <issuer>
        <issuerCik>0001720201</issuerCik>
        <issuerName>iPic Entertainment Inc.</issuerName>
        <issuerTradingSymbol>IPIC</issuerTradingSymbol>
    </issuer>

    <reportingOwner>
        <reportingOwnerId>
            <rptOwnerCik>0001593051</rptOwnerCik>
            <rptOwnerName>Retirement Systems of Alabama</rptOwnerName>
        </reportingOwnerId>
        <reportingOwnerAddress>
            <rptOwnerStreet1>P.O. BOX 302150</rptOwnerStreet1>
            <rptOwnerStreet2></rptOwnerStreet2>
            <rptOwnerCity>MONTGOMERY</rptOwnerCity>
            <rptOwnerState>AL</rptOwnerState>
            <rptOwnerZipCode>36130-2150</rptOwnerZipCode>
            <rptOwnerStateDescription></rptOwnerStateDescription>
        </reportingOwnerAddress>
        <reportingOwnerRelationship>
            <isDirector>0</isDirector>
            <isOfficer>0</isOfficer>
            <isTenPercentOwner>0</isTenPercentOwner>
            <isOther>1</isOther>
            <officerTitle></officerTitle>
            <otherText>See explanation below</otherText>
        </reportingOwnerRelationship>
    </reportingOwner>

    <nonDerivativeTable></nonDerivativeTable>

    <derivativeTable></derivativeTable>

    <footnotes></footnotes>

    <remarks>The Retirement Systems of Alabama (&quot;RSA&quot;), the filing person, is a public pension plan statutorily formed under the laws of the State of Alabama.  RSA consists of the Teachers' Retirement System of Alabama and the Employees' Retirement System of Alabama, which includes and administers the Judicial Retirement Fund.  Each system is considered a body corporate of the State of Alabama and they are referred to collectively for financial reporting purposes as &quot;RSA.&quot;  While each system has distinct boards of control, they share executive management and certain other services.  In particular, the investment decisions for each system are made by RSA's investment staff. Because RSA exercises voting and investment power over the Issuer's common stock for the benefit of members of state retirement systems, those securities are excluded from the determination of the RSA's beneficial ownership by virtue of Exchange Act Rule 16a-1(a)(1).  The Form 3 filed on January 31,2018 and the Form 4 filed on July 7, 2018 by the RSA were therefore not required and this Form 4 is being filed solely for the purpose of providing notice that no such filings will be made by RSA with respect to the Issuer's common stock going forward.</remarks>

    <ownerSignature>
        <signatureName>/s/ Marc Green as Chief Investment Officer</signatureName>
        <signatureDate>2019-01-07</signatureDate>
    </ownerSignature>
</ownershipDocument>
