<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ownershipDocument>

    <schemaVersion>X0206</schemaVersion>

    <documentType>3</documentType>

    <periodOfReport>2018-12-31</periodOfReport>

    <noSecuritiesOwned>0</noSecuritiesOwned>

    <issuer>
        <issuerCik>0000825313</issuerCik>
        <issuerName>ALLIANCEBERNSTEIN HOLDING L.P.</issuerName>
        <issuerTradingSymbol>AB</issuerTradingSymbol>
    </issuer>

    <reportingOwner>
        <reportingOwnerId>
            <rptOwnerCik>0001761959</rptOwnerCik>
            <rptOwnerName>Alpha Units Holdings, Inc.</rptOwnerName>
        </reportingOwnerId>
        <reportingOwnerAddress>
            <rptOwnerStreet1>1290 AVENUE OF THE AMERICAS</rptOwnerStreet1>
            <rptOwnerStreet2></rptOwnerStreet2>
            <rptOwnerCity>NEW YORK</rptOwnerCity>
            <rptOwnerState>NY</rptOwnerState>
            <rptOwnerZipCode></rptOwnerZipCode>
            <rptOwnerStateDescription></rptOwnerStateDescription>
        </reportingOwnerAddress>
        <reportingOwnerRelationship>
            <isDirector>0</isDirector>
            <isOfficer>0</isOfficer>
            <isTenPercentOwner>0</isTenPercentOwner>
            <isOther>1</isOther>
            <otherText>See Remarks</otherText>
        </reportingOwnerRelationship>
    </reportingOwner>

    <nonDerivativeTable>
        <nonDerivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Units</value>
                <footnoteId id="F1"/>
            </securityTitle>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>1444356</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F2"/>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>D</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F3"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F4"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F5"/>
                    <footnoteId id="F6"/>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeHolding>
    </nonDerivativeTable>

    <footnotes>
        <footnote id="F1">Units representing assignments of beneficial ownership of limited partnership interests (&quot;Holding Units&quot;) in AllianceBernstein Holding L.P.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F2">On December 31, 2018, ACMC, LLC (&quot;ACMC&quot;) distributed 1,444,356 Holding Units and 74,406,933 units of limited partnership interests of AllianceBernstein L.P. (&quot;AB Capital Units&quot;) to its sole member, AXA Equitable Life Insurance Company (&quot;AXA Equitable&quot;). Upon receipt of the 1,444,356 Holding Units and 74,406,933 AB Capital Units, AXA Equitable immediately contributed the 1,444,356 Holding Units and 74,406,933 AB Capital Units to its wholly owned subsidiary, Alpha Units Holdings, Inc.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F3">AXA S.A. (&quot;AXA&quot;) owns approximately 59.2% of the outstanding common stock of AXA Equitable Holdings, Inc. (&quot;EQH&quot;), a holding company for
a group of insurance and related financial services companies. EQH is the sole member of AXA Equitable Financial Services, LLC, which wholly
owns (i) AXA Equitable, which in turn owns ACMC and (ii) MONY Life Insurance Company of America (&quot;MLOA&quot;). EQH also wholly owns AXA-IM
Holding U.S. Inc. (&quot;AXA-IM Holding&quot;).</footnote>
        <footnote id="F4">As of December 31, 2017, AXA Assurances I.A.R.D. Mutuelle and AXA Assurances Vie Mutuelle (collectively, &quot;Mutuelles AXA&quot;), directly
beneficially owned approximately 14.13% of the issued ordinary shares (representing approximately 23.97% of the voting power) of AXA. The
Mutuelles AXA and AXA expressly declare that the filing of this Form 3 shall not be construed as an admission that either of them is, for
purposes of Section 16 of the Securities Exchange Act of 1934, the beneficial owner of any securities covered by this Form 3.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F5">In addition to the Holding Units reported in this Form 3, the Reporting Person and its affiliates beneficially own additional Holding Units and AB Capital Units as follows. As of the close of business on December 31, 2018, EQH beneficially owned directly 2,566,838 Holding Units and 51,192,758 AB Capital Units; AXA-IM Holding beneficially owned directly 41,934,582 AB Capital Units; MLOA beneficially owned directly 2,587,472 AB Capital Units; Alpha Units Holdings, Inc. beneficially owned directly 74,406,933 AB Capital Units; and AllianceBernstein Corporation, a wholly owned subsidiary of Alpha Units Holdings, Inc., owned a 1% general partnership interest in AllianceBernstein L.P. and 100,000 units of general partnership interest in AllianceBernstein Holding L.P.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F6">The AB Capital Units are highly illiquid, and the ability of a holder of AB Capital Units to exchange them in the future for Holding Units if it so desires is substantially limited. In general, transfers of AB Capital Units will be allowed only with the written consent of both AXA Equitable and the general partner of AllianceBernstein. AXA Equitable and the general partner of AllianceBernstein have stated that they intend to refuse to consent to any transfer that is not described in the safe harbors set forth in the United States Treasury regulations.</footnote>
    </footnotes>

    <remarks>Affiliate of holder of general partnership units.</remarks>

    <ownerSignature>
        <signatureName>/s/ Anders B. Malmstrom, Chairman of the Board, President and Chief Executive Officer</signatureName>
        <signatureDate>2019-01-03</signatureDate>
    </ownerSignature>
</ownershipDocument>
