<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ownershipDocument>

    <schemaVersion>X0306</schemaVersion>

    <documentType>4</documentType>

    <periodOfReport>2019-01-07</periodOfReport>

    <notSubjectToSection16>0</notSubjectToSection16>

    <issuer>
        <issuerCik>0000910406</issuerCik>
        <issuerName>HAIN CELESTIAL GROUP INC</issuerName>
        <issuerTradingSymbol>HAIN</issuerTradingSymbol>
    </issuer>

    <reportingOwner>
        <reportingOwnerId>
            <rptOwnerCik>0001580771</rptOwnerCik>
            <rptOwnerName>Welling Glenn W.</rptOwnerName>
        </reportingOwnerId>
        <reportingOwnerAddress>
            <rptOwnerStreet1>C/O ENGAGED CAPITAL, LLC</rptOwnerStreet1>
            <rptOwnerStreet2>610 NEWPORT CENTER DRIVE, SUITE 250</rptOwnerStreet2>
            <rptOwnerCity>NEWPORT BEACH</rptOwnerCity>
            <rptOwnerState>CA</rptOwnerState>
            <rptOwnerZipCode>92660</rptOwnerZipCode>
            <rptOwnerStateDescription></rptOwnerStateDescription>
        </reportingOwnerAddress>
        <reportingOwnerRelationship>
            <isDirector>1</isDirector>
            <isOfficer>0</isOfficer>
            <isTenPercentOwner>1</isTenPercentOwner>
            <isOther>0</isOther>
            <officerTitle></officerTitle>
            <otherText></otherText>
        </reportingOwnerRelationship>
    </reportingOwner>

    <nonDerivativeTable>
        <nonDerivativeTransaction>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Common Stock</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <transactionDate>
                <value>2019-01-07</value>
            </transactionDate>
            <transactionCoding>
                <transactionFormType>4</transactionFormType>
                <transactionCode>A</transactionCode>
                <equitySwapInvolved>0</equitySwapInvolved>
            </transactionCoding>
            <transactionAmounts>
                <transactionShares>
                    <value>14220</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F1"/>
                </transactionShares>
                <transactionPricePerShare>
                    <value>17.44</value>
                </transactionPricePerShare>
                <transactionAcquiredDisposedCode>
                    <value>A</value>
                </transactionAcquiredDisposedCode>
            </transactionAmounts>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>21577</value>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>D</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeTransaction>
        <nonDerivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Common Stock</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>2117002</value>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>By: Engaged Capital Co-Invest VI, LP</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F2"/>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeHolding>
        <nonDerivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Common Stock</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>4412690</value>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>By: Engaged Capital Co-Invest VI-A, LP</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F3"/>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeHolding>
        <nonDerivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Common Stock</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>1382115</value>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>By: Engaged Capital Flagship Master Fund, LP</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F4"/>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeHolding>
        <nonDerivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Common Stock</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>1407543</value>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>By: Engaged Capital Co-Invest VI-C, LP</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F5"/>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeHolding>
        <nonDerivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Common Stock</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>119487</value>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>By: Managed Account of Engaged Capital, LLC</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F6"/>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeHolding>
        <nonDerivativeHolding>
            <securityTitle>
                <value>Common Stock</value>
            </securityTitle>
            <postTransactionAmounts>
                <sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
                    <value>2322405</value>
                </sharesOwnedFollowingTransaction>
            </postTransactionAmounts>
            <ownershipNature>
                <directOrIndirectOwnership>
                    <value>I</value>
                </directOrIndirectOwnership>
                <natureOfOwnership>
                    <value>By: Engaged Capital Co-Invest VI-B, LP</value>
                    <footnoteId id="F7"/>
                </natureOfOwnership>
            </ownershipNature>
        </nonDerivativeHolding>
    </nonDerivativeTable>

    <derivativeTable></derivativeTable>

    <footnotes>
        <footnote id="F1">Represents a grant of restricted shares of the Issuer's common stock, which will vest on October 29, 2019.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F2">Securities held directly by Engaged Capital Co-Invest VI, LP (&quot;Engaged Capital Co-Invest VI&quot;). Mr. Welling, by virtue of his position as the founder and Chief Investment Officer of Engaged Capital, the general partner and investment adviser of Engaged Capital Co-Invest VI, and as the sole member of Engaged Holdings, the managing member of Engaged Capital, may be deemed to beneficially own the securities owned directly by Engaged Capital Co-Invest VI for purposes of Section 16. Mr. Welling expressly disclaims beneficial ownership of such securities except to the extent of his pecuniary interest therein.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F3">Securities held directly by Engaged Capital Co-Invest VI-A, LP (&quot;Engaged Capital Co-Invest VI-A&quot;). Mr. Welling, by virtue of his position as the founder and Chief Investment Officer of Engaged Capital, the general partner and investment adviser of Engaged Capital Co-Invest VI-A, and as the sole member of Engaged Holdings, the managing member of Engaged Capital, may be deemed to beneficially own the securities owned directly by Engaged Capital Co-Invest VI-A for purposes of Section 16. Mr. Welling expressly disclaims beneficial ownership of such securities except to the extent of his pecuniary interest therein.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F4">Securities held directly by Engaged Capital Flagship Master Fund, LP (&quot;Engaged Capital Master&quot;). Mr. Welling, by virtue of his position as the founder and Chief Investment Officer of Engaged Capital, the general partner and investment adviser of Engaged Capital Master, and as the sole member of Engaged Holdings, the managing member of Engaged Capital, may be deemed to beneficially own the securities owned directly by Engaged Capital Master for purposes of Section 16. Mr. Welling expressly disclaims beneficial ownership of such securities except to the extent of his pecuniary interest therein.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F5">Securities held directly by Engaged Capital Co-Invest VI-C, LP (&quot;Engaged Capital Co-Invest VI-C&quot;). Glenn W. Welling, by virtue of his position as the founder and Chief Investment Officer of Engaged Capital, LLC (&quot;Engaged Capital&quot;), the general partner and investment adviser of Engaged Capital Co-Invest VI-C, and as the sole member of Engaged Capital Holdings, LLC (&quot;Engaged Holdings&quot;), the managing member of Engaged Capital, may be deemed to beneficially own the securities owned directly by Engaged Capital Co-Invest VI-C for purposes of Section 16. Mr. Welling expressly disclaims beneficial ownership of such securities except to the extent of his pecuniary interest therein.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F6">Securities held in an account separately managed by Engaged Capital (the &quot;Engaged Capital Account&quot;). Mr. Welling, by virtue of his position as the founder and Chief Investment Officer of Engaged Capital, the investment adviser of the Engaged Capital Account, and as the sole member of Engaged Holdings, the managing member of Engaged Capital, may be deemed to beneficially own the securities held in the Engaged Capital Account for purposes of Section 16. Mr. Welling expressly disclaims beneficial ownership of such securities except to the extent of his pecuniary interest therein.</footnote>
        <footnote id="F7">Securities held directly by Engaged Capital Co-Invest VI-B, LP (&quot;Engaged Capital Co-Invest VI-B&quot;). Mr. Welling, by virtue of his position as the founder and Chief Investment Officer of Engaged Capital, the general partner and investment adviser of Engaged Capital Co-Invest VI-B, and as the sole member of Engaged Holdings, the managing member of Engaged Capital, may be deemed to beneficially own the securities owned directly by Engaged Capital Co-Invest VI-B for purposes of Section 16. Mr. Welling expressly disclaims beneficial ownership of such securities except to the extent of his pecuniary interest therein.</footnote>
    </footnotes>

    <remarks></remarks>

    <ownerSignature>
        <signatureName>/s/ Glenn W. Welling</signatureName>
        <signatureDate>2019-01-09</signatureDate>
    </ownerSignature>
</ownershipDocument>
